(Howard:)...I go with Raj to scam on hippie chicks
at the farmer's market...
(Howard:)...but he's still working with Sheldon.
(Howard:)So I thought I'd come over here
and make scrambled eggs and salami.
It's the perfect meal for après l'amour.
[PENNY GROANS]
(Penny:)Kill me.
(Howard:)By the way, I couldn't help overhearing
your big finish. Bravo, Leonard.
(Penny:)See, if you had killed me
when I said "kill me"...
(Penny:)...I wouldn't have had to hear that.
(Howard:)What do you guys think?
Wanna take in a matinée? Go rollerblading?
(Howard:)Catch a step class?
(Penny:)-Do something.
-Yeah. Okay. Um....
(Leonard:)Howard, we need to talk.
Sure. What's up, homes?
[STAMMERS]
(Leonard:)Please understand that it's not
that we don't want you around.
(Leonard:)But Penny and I
occasionally need some alone time.
(Howard:)Oh.
I get it. I'm the third wheel. Heh.